[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "How likely is it that this hurricane could build up and hit Tampa?", "question_tokens": ["How", "likely", "is", "it", "that", "this", "hurricane", "could", "build", "up", "and", "hit", "Tampa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Yes, you know, at least 10 percent now.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "at", "least", "10", "percent", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tampa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "And regardless of whether the eye of the storm hits Tampa, is it pretty likely that Tampa would get some pretty extreme weather anyway?", "question_tokens": ["And", "regardless", "of", "whether", "the", "eye", "of", "the", "storm", "hits", "Tampa", ",", "is", "it", "pretty", "likely", "that", "Tampa", "would", "get", "some", "pretty", "extreme", "weather", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tampa", "Tampa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "So is it -- is it take the willies time or something a little stronger?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "take", "the", "willies", "time", "or", "something", "a", "little", "stronger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "It's going to take -- it's going to take a couple of days for me to know it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "take", "--", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "take", "a", "couple", "of", "days", "for", "me", "to", "know", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Or could this really bring the social issues of the right wing of the conservatives to the fore on this convention which could be damaging to Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "could", "this", "really", "bring", "the", "social", "issues", "of", "the", "right", "wing", "of", "the", "conservatives", "to", "the", "fore", "on", "this", "convention", "which", "could", "be", "damaging", "to", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, it might be a little bit more of the latter.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "might", "be", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "of", "the", "latter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio", "Pennsylvania", "Florida"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "When people hear this and see this, they don't really know what they're voting for, do they, Bill?", "question_tokens": ["When", "people", "hear", "this", "and", "see", "this", ",", "they", "do", "n't", "really", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "voting", "for", ",", "do", "they", ",", "Bill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, I think that in order for Romney to win, he's going to need minorities, he's going to need women, he's going to need swing states like Ohio and Pennsylvania and Florida.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "in", "order", "for", "Romney", "to", "win", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "need", "minorities", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "need", "women", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "need", "swing", "states", "like", "Ohio", "and", "Pennsylvania", "and", "Florida", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Where's the consistency here, Amy?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "'s", "the", "consistency", "here", ",", "Amy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, you know, I can't speak for Mitt Romney and his flip-flopping.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "speak", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "and", "his", "flip-flopping", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "If it comes down to money buying an election, that can't be good for America democracy, can it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "comes", "down", "to", "money", "buying", "an", "election", ",", "that", "ca", "n't", "be", "good", "for", "America", "democracy", ",", "can", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Do you feel comfortable as a Republican that it could come down to firepower and money from super PACs?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "comfortable", "as", "a", "Republican", "that", "it", "could", "come", "down", "to", "firepower", "and", "money", "from", "super", "PACs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, a couple of corrections.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "couple", "of", "corrections", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "VBD", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 285, "question": "It's higher than when he took office?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "higher", "than", "when", "he", "took", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "It's 7.8 was the --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "7.8", "was", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2010"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "WDT", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Are they going to punish him in November, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "going", "to", "punish", "him", "in", "November", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, we saw in 2010 that voters punished this unemployment rate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "saw", "in", "2010", "that", "voters", "punished", "this", "unemployment", "rate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Missouri"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Well, he's not going to step down because he's going to be a sympathetic figure for the far right within Missouri.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "step", "down", "because", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "sympathetic", "figure", "for", "the", "far", "right", "within", "Missouri", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Or for women's rights more, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "for", "women", "'s", "rights", "more", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "RBR", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "But in getting Americans back to work, Barack Obama has not been very successful, has he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "getting", "Americans", "back", "to", "work", ",", "Barack", "Obama", "has", "not", "been", "very", "successful", ",", "has", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "NNPS", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "OK, the final record is not yet a success.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "the", "final", "record", "is", "not", "yet", "a", "success", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What is your honest assessment of his performance as president in the last four years?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "honest", "assessment", "of", "his", "performance", "as", "president", "in", "the", "last", "four", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I start with a bias.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "start", "with", "a", "bias", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What's his biggest fault?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "his", "biggest", "fault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "It's that sometimes he's too cool.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "that", "sometimes", "he", "'s", "too", "cool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Do you still get as much fun out of it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "get", "as", "much", "fun", "out", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "It's the audience.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "audience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What do you say to friends of yours like mine that say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "friends", "of", "yours", "like", "mine", "that", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, the honest answer is, you saw the passion I have about politics, and I really do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "honest", "answer", "is", ",", "you", "saw", "the", "passion", "I", "have", "about", "politics", ",", "and", "I", "really", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC Universal"]}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Will you ever quit that show?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "ever", "quit", "that", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I've told NBC Universal that I am going to stop.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "told", "NBC", "Universal", "that", "I", "am", "going", "to", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "When I'm 104.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "'m", "104", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "So next year?", "question_tokens": ["So", "next", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "That's great.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "That's next year then?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "next", "year", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]